[
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0000_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0000_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0000_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0001_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0001_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0002_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0002_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0003_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0003_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0003_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0004_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0005_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0005_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0006_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0006_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0006_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0007_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0008_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "38.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0009_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0009_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0009_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0010_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0010_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0012_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0012_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0012_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0013_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0013_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0013_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0014_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0016_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0016_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0016_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0017_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0017_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0017_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0018_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0020_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0020_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0021_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0022_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0022_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "40.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0023_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0024_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0024_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0024_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0026_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0027_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0027_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0027_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0028_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0029_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0029_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0029_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0031_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0031_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0031_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0032_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0032_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0033_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "39.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0034_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0034_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0034_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0035_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0035_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0036_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0036_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0037_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0038_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "48.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0038_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0038_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "45.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0039_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0039_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0040_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0040_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0041_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0041_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0042_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0042_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0042_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0043_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0043_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0044_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0044_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0044_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0045_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0045_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0047_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0048_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0048_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0049_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0051_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0051_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0051_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0051_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0052_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0052_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0052_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0053_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0054_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0055_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0055_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0055_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0056_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0056_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0057_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0057_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0058_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0058_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0059_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0059_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0059_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0060_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0060_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0061_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0061_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0062_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0062_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0062_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0065_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0065_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0065_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0066_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0067_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0067_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0067_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0068_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0068_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0069_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0070_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0071_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0072_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0072_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0072_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0073_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0073_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0073_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0073_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0074_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0074_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0074_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0075_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0076_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0078_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0078_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0078_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0079_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "46.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0079_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0080_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0080_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0080_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0082_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0083_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0083_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0085_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0085_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0087_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0087_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0087_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0089_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0089_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0089_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0090_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0091_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0092_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0092_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0092_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0092_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0092_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0093_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0093_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0093_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0094_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0096_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0096_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0096_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0097_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0098_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0098_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0099_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0099_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0101_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0101_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0101_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0101_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0101_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0101_05",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0102_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0102_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0103_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0103_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0104_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0105_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0105_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0105_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0106_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0106_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0106_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0107_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0108_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0109_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0109_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0110_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0110_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0110_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0111_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0111_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0111_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0112_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0112_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0112_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0113_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0113_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0114_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0114_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0114_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0115_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0115_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0115_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0116_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0116_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0116_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0117_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0118_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0118_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0118_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0119_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0120_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0120_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0121_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0121_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0121_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0122_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0122_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0123_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "38.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0123_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0123_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0124_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0124_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0125_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0126_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0126_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0126_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0127_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0127_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0128_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0129_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0130_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0132_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0132_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0132_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0133_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0134_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0134_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0134_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0135_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0136_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0136_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0136_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0137_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0137_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0137_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0138_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0140_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0140_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0141_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0141_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0141_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0142_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0142_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0143_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0143_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0143_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0145_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0147_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0147_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0148_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0150_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0150_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0150_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0151_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "47.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0151_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0152_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "48.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0152_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "64.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0152_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "79.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0154_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0155_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0155_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0155_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0156_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0157_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0157_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0158_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0158_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0158_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0159_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0160_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0160_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0160_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0160_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0160_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0161_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0161_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0161_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0162_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0163_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0163_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0165_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0165_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0165_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0166_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0166_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0166_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0167_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0168_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0168_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0168_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0170_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0170_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0170_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0171_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0171_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0172_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0172_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0173_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0173_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0173_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0174_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0174_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0175_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0176_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0177_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0177_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0177_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0178_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0179_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0180_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0181_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0181_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0181_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0181_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0182_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0182_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0182_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0183_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0184_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0185_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "67.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0186_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0186_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0188_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0189_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "94.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0190_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0191_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0191_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0191_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0192_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0192_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0192_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0194_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0195_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0195_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0195_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0197_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0197_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0197_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0198_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0199_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0200_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0200_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0200_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0201_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0201_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0201_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0202_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0204_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0204_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0204_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0205_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0205_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0205_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0206_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0206_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0206_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0209_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0209_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0209_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0210_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0210_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0211_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0211_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0211_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0211_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0212_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0212_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0212_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0213_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0214_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0214_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0214_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0215_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0215_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0216_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0218_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "46.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0218_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0219_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0220_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0220_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0220_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0223_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0223_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0223_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0224_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0225_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "44.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0226_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0226_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0227_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0228_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0229_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0229_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0229_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0230_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0232_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0232_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0232_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0233_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0233_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0234_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0235_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0236_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0236_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0237_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0237_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0238_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0238_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0239_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0239_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0239_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0240_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0241_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0241_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0241_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0242_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0242_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0242_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0243_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0244_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0244_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0245_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0247_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0247_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0248_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0248_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0248_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0250_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0250_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0250_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0252_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0253_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0254_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0254_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0255_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0255_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0255_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0258_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0259_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0259_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0260_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0260_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0260_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0261_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0261_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0261_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0261_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0262_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0262_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0263_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0263_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0264_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0264_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0264_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0265_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0265_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0265_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0266_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0266_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0267_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0268_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0268_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0268_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0269_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0269_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0269_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0270_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0270_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0270_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0271_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0271_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0272_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0272_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0273_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0273_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0274_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0274_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0274_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0275_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0276_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0276_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0279_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0279_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0279_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0280_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0280_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0280_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0281_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "50.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0282_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0282_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0282_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0283_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0284_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0285_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0286_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0286_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0286_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0286_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0287_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0288_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0288_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0288_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0289_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0289_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0290_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0291_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0291_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0291_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0292_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0292_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0293_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0293_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0294_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0294_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0294_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0295_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0295_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0296_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0296_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0297_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0297_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0297_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0298_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0299_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0299_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0301_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0301_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0301_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0302_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0302_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0303_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0303_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0303_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0305_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0305_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0306_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0306_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0308_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0309_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0309_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0310_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0310_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0310_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0311_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0312_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0312_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "58.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0312_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "49.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0313_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0313_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0313_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0315_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "39.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0317_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0317_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "44.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0318_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0319_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0320_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0320_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0320_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0320_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0321_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0322_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0323_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0323_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0324_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0324_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0325_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0325_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0326_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0327_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0330_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0331_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0331_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0332_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0332_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0332_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0333_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0335_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0335_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0335_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0336_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0336_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0337_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0337_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0337_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0339_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0340_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0340_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0340_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0341_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0341_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0344_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0344_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0345_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0345_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0346_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0346_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0347_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0347_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0347_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0348_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0348_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0348_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0349_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0349_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0350_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0350_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0350_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0352_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0352_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0352_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0358_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0358_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0358_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0359_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0359_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0360_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0361_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0361_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0361_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0362_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0362_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0362_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0362_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0363_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0364_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0364_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0365_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0365_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0365_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0366_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0367_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0367_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0368_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0368_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0369_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0369_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0369_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0370_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0370_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "45.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0370_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0371_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0371_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0372_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0373_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0373_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0374_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0375_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0375_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0375_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0376_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0376_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0376_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0379_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0380_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0380_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0380_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0381_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0381_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0381_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0383_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0383_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0383_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0384_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0385_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0385_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0385_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0386_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0387_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "39.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0387_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0387_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "40.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0388_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0388_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0390_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0391_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0392_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0392_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0392_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0393_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0393_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0393_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0394_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0394_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0395_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0395_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0395_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0396_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0396_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0396_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0397_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0397_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0398_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0398_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0399_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0399_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0400_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0400_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0401_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0402_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0403_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0403_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0404_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0404_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0404_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0405_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0407_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0407_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0408_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0408_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0409_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0409_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0410_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0410_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0411_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "45.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0411_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0411_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0413_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0415_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0415_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0415_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0416_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0416_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0416_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0416_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0416_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0417_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0418_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0418_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0418_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0419_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0419_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0419_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0420_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0420_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0420_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0421_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0421_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0421_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0422_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0424_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0424_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0424_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0425_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0425_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0428_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0428_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0429_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0431_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0433_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0434_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0434_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0434_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0436_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0437_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0437_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0438_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0439_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0439_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0440_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0440_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0440_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0442_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0443_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0444_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0444_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0445_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0445_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0446_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0446_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0447_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0447_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0447_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0448_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0448_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0448_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0449_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0449_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0449_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0450_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0451_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0451_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0451_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0451_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0451_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0451_05",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0452_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0452_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0452_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0453_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0453_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "50.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0454_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0455_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0456_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0456_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0457_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0457_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0457_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0459_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0459_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0460_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0463_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0463_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0464_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0465_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0465_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0466_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0466_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "47.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0467_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0468_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0468_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0468_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0469_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0469_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0469_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0470_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0470_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0471_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0471_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0471_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0472_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0472_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0472_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0473_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0473_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0475_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "48.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0475_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "46.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0475_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0476_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0476_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0476_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0477_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0477_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0478_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0478_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0479_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0479_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0479_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0480_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0480_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0481_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0481_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0482_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0482_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0483_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0484_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0484_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0485_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0486_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0487_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0487_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0489_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0489_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0489_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0491_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0492_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0492_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0493_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0493_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0495_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0497_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "81.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0498_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0498_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0498_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0499_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "49.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0501_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0501_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0501_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0502_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0502_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0502_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0503_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0504_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0505_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0505_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0505_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0505_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0505_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0506_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0507_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0508_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0508_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0508_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0509_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0509_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0509_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0510_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0510_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0510_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0511_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0511_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0512_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0513_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0514_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0514_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0515_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0515_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0515_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0516_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0516_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0517_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0517_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0517_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0519_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0520_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0520_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "49.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0521_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0522_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0523_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0523_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0523_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0524_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0524_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0525_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0525_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0525_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0526_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0526_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0528_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0528_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0529_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0529_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0529_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0530_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0531_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0532_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0532_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0533_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0533_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "59.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0534_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0534_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0536_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0536_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0536_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0537_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0538_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0539_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0539_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0539_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0540_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0540_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0540_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0541_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0541_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0541_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0542_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0543_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0543_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0543_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0544_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0545_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0545_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0545_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0546_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0547_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0547_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0547_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0548_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0548_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0548_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0551_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0554_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0554_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0555_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0556_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0556_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0557_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0557_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0557_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0560_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0561_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0561_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0562_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0563_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0564_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0566_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0567_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0567_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0569_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0569_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0570_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0570_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0570_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0571_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0571_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0572_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0572_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0572_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0573_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0573_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0576_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0576_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0576_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0577_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0579_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0579_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0579_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0581_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0581_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0581_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0582_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0582_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0582_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0584_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0584_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0584_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0585_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0585_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0586_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "6.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0586_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0586_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0587_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0587_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0587_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0587_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0588_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "89.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0588_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "76.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0588_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "67.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0588_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "78.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0589_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0589_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0589_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0590_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0590_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0592_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "54.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0592_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "53.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0594_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0596_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0596_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0596_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0597_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0597_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0597_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0600_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0600_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0600_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0601_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0601_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0602_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0603_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0603_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0604_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0604_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0604_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0605_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0605_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0610_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0610_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0610_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0611_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0611_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0612_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0612_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0613_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0613_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0613_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0614_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0614_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0614_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0615_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0615_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0617_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0619_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0620_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0620_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0622_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0622_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0623_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0623_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0624_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0625_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0625_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0626_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0626_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0626_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0627_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0627_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0628_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0628_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0628_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0630_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0630_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0630_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0630_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0630_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0630_05",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0630_06",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0631_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0631_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0631_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0632_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0634_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0635_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0635_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0636_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0637_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0638_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0639_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0640_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0640_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0640_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0641_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0642_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0642_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0642_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0642_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0646_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0646_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0646_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0649_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0649_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0650_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0654_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0654_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0656_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0656_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0656_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0656_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0657_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0659_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0659_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0661_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0662_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0662_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0662_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0666_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0666_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0666_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0667_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "82.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0667_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "59.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0667_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "78.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0668_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0669_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0669_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0672_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0672_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0673_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0673_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0673_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0673_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0673_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "49.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0673_05",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "48.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0674_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0674_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0675_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0675_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0676_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0676_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0677_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0677_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0677_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0679_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0679_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0680_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0680_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0681_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0682_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0683_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0687_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0688_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0691_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0691_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0692_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0692_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0692_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0692_03",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0692_04",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0694_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "38.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0694_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0698_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0698_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0703_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0703_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0705_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0705_01",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0705_02",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannet",
        "scene_name": "scene0706_00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "56a0ec536c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8b5caf3398",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "98b4ec142f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "43.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "fe1733741f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "51.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "41b00feddb",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "40.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b20a261fdf",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "5fb5d2dbf2",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f8f12e4e6b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e9ac2fc517",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "92.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "0b031f3119",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "40b56bf310",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e3ecd49e2b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "9f139a318d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "419cbe7c11",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "39f36da05b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "7cd2ac43b4",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "fb05e13ad1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bc03d88fc3",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f34d532901",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "75d29d69b8",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c413b34238",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ccfd3ed9c7",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "aaa11940d3",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "4a1a3a7dc5",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8d563fc2cc",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1841a0b525",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "07f5b601ee",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "28a9ee4557",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "785e7504b9",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "37.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1366d5ae89",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "d2f44bf242",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "2e74812d00",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "0cf2e9402d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "2a496183e1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "281bc17764",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bc400d86e1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "30966f4c6e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "260fa55d50",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8b2c0938d6",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e050c15a8d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "60.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a4e227f506",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "59e3f1ea37",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ef18cf0708",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "036bce3393",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "44.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "faec2f0468",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "9b74afd2d2",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "4ba22fa7e4",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "302a7f6b67",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "49a82360aa",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "824d9cfa6e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "25927bb04c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "4c5c60fa76",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1a8e0d78c0",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "394a542a19",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e0abd740ba",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "260db9cf5a",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e9e16b6043",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8e00ac7f59",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c0c863b72d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a1d9da703c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ad2d07fd11",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c24f94007b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a05ee63164",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e1b1d9de55",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f07340dfea",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "d6d9ddb03f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "cbd4b3055e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "acd69a1746",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bf6e439e38",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "52599ae063",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "55b2bf8036",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "303745abc7",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8a20d62ac0",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c545851c4f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b08a908f0f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "7e7cd69a59",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "107.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "961911d451",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "50809ea0d8",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e91722b5a3",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "30f4a2b44d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1204e08f17",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "94ee15e8ba",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e8e81396b6",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "2b1dc6d6a5",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1d003b07bd",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a08dda47a8",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b5918e4637",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f8062cb7ce",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e898c76c1f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "689fec23d7",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "210f741378",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "45.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ab6983ae6c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "35.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "355e5e32db",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "53.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "d6702c681d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "37ea1c52f0",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bc2fce1d81",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1b75758486",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "7977624358",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ed2216380b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f25f5e6f63",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "646af5e14b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "29.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "dfac5b38df",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ef25276c25",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "116456116b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1ae9e5d2a6",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "47b37eb6f9",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "147.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "712dc47104",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "80ffca8a48",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "47.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "07ff1c45bb",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f6659a3107",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "daffc70503",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "076c822ecc",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "89.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "5a269ba6fe",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "89214f3ca0",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "27.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "9471b8d485",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "45d2e33be1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "08bbbdcc3d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "54.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "69e5939669",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "51.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "dc263dfbf0",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "54.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "98fe276aa8",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "9859de300f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b73f5cdc41",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ada5304e41",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f5401524e5",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "d415cc449b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bd9305480d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1831b3823a",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ebc200e928",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "66c98f4a9b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "87f6d7d564",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "0a5c013435",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "2970e95b65",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "52.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "0e75f3c4d9",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "53.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "480ddaadc0",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "4ea827f5a1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "be0ed6b33c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "88627b561e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "73.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "13285009a4",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "28.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "108ec0b806",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "33.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "3e928dc2f6",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b1d75ecd55",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b97261909e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "88cf747085",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "6cc2231b9c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b09431c547",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "1.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c9abde4c4b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c8f2218ee2",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e01b287af5",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "85251de7d1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "4.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1b9692f0c7",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "16c9bd2e1e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a08d9a2476",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "290ef3f2c9",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "61adeff7d5",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a5114ca13d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "7.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "6f1848d1e3",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "281ba69af1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "60.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "104acbf7d2",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "26.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8890d0a267",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c0f5742640",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "67d702f2e8",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1f7cbbdde1",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "079a326597",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "0a184cf634",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "7f4d173c9c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "24.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a29cccc784",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "3f1e1610de",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "36.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "709ab5bffe",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "2.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "6464461276",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "7e09430da7",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "324d07a5b3",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bb87c292ad",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "41.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8a35ef3cfe",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "9460c8889d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "95.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "3c95c89d61",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "d918af9c5f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "73.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ab11145646",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "25.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "7eac902fd5",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "3.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "d6cbe4b28b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "39.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ef69d58016",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8be0cd3817",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "22.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8f82c394d6",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "9.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "5d152fab1b",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "6d89a7320d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "0a7cc12c0e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "4318f8bb3c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "15.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "893fb90e89",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c47168fab2",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8133208cb6",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "280b83fcf3",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "61.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "410c470782",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "50.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e7ac609391",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "31.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "4422722c49",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "9f79564dbf",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "59.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "f248c2bcdc",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "30.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "5654092cc2",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "ab046f8faf",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "95d525fbfd",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "66.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "8e6ff28354",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "32.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c173f62b15",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "42.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c856c41c99",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "d7abfc4b17",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "32280ecbca",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "6855e1ac32",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "5656608266",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "12.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "0a76e06478",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "39e6ee46df",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "55.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e0de253456",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "a003a6585e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "19.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "6b40d1a939",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "eb4bc76767",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "21.2",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "cf1ffd871d",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.3",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "b26e64c4b0",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "13.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "e8ea9b4da8",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "14.1",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bd7375297e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "18.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "54b6127146",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "6ee2fc1070",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "bfd3fd54d2",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "11.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "484ad681df",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "23.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "7079b59642",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "9f21bdec45",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "5.4",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1c4b893630",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "8.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "251443268c",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "10.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "fd361ab85f",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "320c3af000",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "20.9",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c5f701a8c7",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "34.6",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "3928249b53",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.5",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "c06a983e63",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.7",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "09bced689e",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "17.0",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    },
    {
        "dataset": "scannetpp",
        "scene_name": "1a130d092a",
        "question_type": "room_size_estimation",
        "question": "What is the size of this room (in square meters)? If multiple rooms are shown, estimate the size of the combined space.",
        "answer": "16.8",
        "object_ids": [],
        "object_labels": []
    }
]